The cradle will fall
Baby Blues is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Amardeep Kaleka.
On a secluded family farm, a mother suffers a psychotic break due to postpartum depression, forcing
the eldest son to protect his sibling from the mother they have always known and loved.
Mom, played by Colleen Porch.
Baby Nathan, played by Aiden Kersh.
Jimmy, played by Ridge Canipe.
Jake, played by Sean Johnson.
Sammy, played by Holden Thomas Maynard.
Cathy, played by Kali Majors.
Baby Blues (also known as Cradle Will Fall) is a 2008 American psychological horror film co-directed by Lars Jacobson and Amar Kaleka,
loosely based on the 2001 killings of five children by their mother Andrea Yates, although the film is set in the 1980s.
It was filmed entirely in Savannah, Georgia by the
company Neverending Light Productions.
The film explores themes of based on true story, slasher, killer mother.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.